London in the 1960's. Everyone had
a story about the Krays.
You could walk into any pub to
hear a lie or two about them.
But I was there
and I'm not careless with the truth.
They were brothers, but bound by more
than blood. They were twins as well.
Counterparts. Gangster-princes
of the city they meant to conquer.
Ron Kray was a one-man London mob.
Bloodthirsty, illogical
and funny as well.
My Reggie was different.
Once in a lifetime do
you find a street fighting man like Reg.
Believe me when I say it took a lot of
love for me to hate him the way I do.
Good morning, Albie.
Good morning, sir.
Tea for two?
Yeah, Albie.
Hello, boys!
How you doing? You all right? Put
your cup of tea in, do you fancy it?
Yeah?
No?
What's this? The old Dagenham Angila?
Ought to
60 in .. what? 40 minutes
or sommit like that?
Cor, it's a bit of you in that, innit? All
black and cramped and very sharp. Yeah.
This one's really milky... for you.
Why don't you fuck off, Kray?
Oh, I will, I will.
Y'know, I don't want to keep you,
you know, what with them... them,
y'know, rapists and murderers you
got to lock away, eh Nipper?
Where do you take a turd in there?
Probably just hold it in, don't you?
Alright, then, have a lovely day. Cheer up.
It's nearly Christmas.
Forget about that.
Where's me driver, where's Frank? He can't
get out of bed in the morning, Reg.
He what? He ain't here, he ain't showed up.
He's heart ain't in it.
Alright. OK, well let's
go get him then, should
we? Where is he? On
Ormsby Street, yeah?
Yeah, come and jump in.
I'll give you a lift. Nah, you're
alright, I'm going to walk. It's
a lovely day for it.
Don't forget this lot.
They're very important I won't.
Come on!
I shall walk incredibly slowly!
Hi, Vera. How you doing?
You good? Yeah. Lovely.
Rita, I was gonna knock on your door.
But me
mum said you left that
in her kitchen. I did!
Is that yours?
It is! Oh, thanks ever so much!
No problem, you're welcome.
Thanks, Reg.
Eastenders.
They won't talk to a policeman,
but they'll kiss a gangster. Ey?
Filthy, cockney bastards.
How about we clean your car for ya?
Is Frank about?
Frank!
Who are you?
I'm Frances. Frank's sister.
Hear about, I recognize you.
See, I recognize you. You was
a little bit younger, then.
You got grown up, didn't ya?
It happens.
What have you got there?
A sweet.
That's not any sweet, is it? That's a Lemon
Sherbert, that is. Mind if I have a crack?
Go on.
Thanks.
Ah, that's nice, innit?
You're not supposed to chew it!
No?
How else am I supposed to
get to the sherbie bit?
By being patient.
Nah.
Being patient doesn't get
you what you want, does it?
Half a minute,
Reg. Be right down.
Is he in trouble?
Yea, he is.
Will you go out with me?
I'll go easy on him if you do.
Alright, but not for that reason.
Saturday night?
Who are you talking to?
You're half-dressed talking
to a man in the door. What's
wrong with you, Frances?
Get back in the kitchen. Finish
them dishes. This is yours.
Thank you.
If you oversleep again, Frank,
alright? It's back to the cheese shop.
Or the fish shop, or whatever
shop it is you come from. Print.
Print shop.
Oh yeah? Well you'll be back to the
fucking shit shop, you understand? Yup.
What does your sister do?
Oh, she goes to one
of those, uh, Pitman
colleges. Y'know? Typing? Shorthand?
Yeah?
Well she's got a bit of class, mate.
She's
very elegant. Where have
you been hiding her?
She's been away.
She's a bit, umm, fragile, Reg.
Oh yeah?
Yeah.
Hmm.
Stop here, Frank.
Four minutes. One job.
How long do you think
it will take for him to
figure it, Albie?
A little bit of cat and mouse.
Nipper Read was the copper on the Krays
case and he made his presence known.
He was heavy-footed, as they say.
So I stared at the back
of this geezer's head
and the whole time I'm thinking...
umm:
Give Ron Kray your sausage.
Give Ron...
your fucking sausage.
Y'know?
I was drilling my eyes into
the back of his head...
Until I'm not even thinking it anymore.
I'm not even thinking.
I'm broadcasting it.
Until he turns around and you
know what he says? He says...
"Hey, Ron, do you fancy my sausage?
I've got no appetite for it."
Interesting.
When my future brother in law
said 'interesting'... Ain't it?
It meant he had no
fucking idea what he, or
you or anyone else was
talking about.
Fascinating, Ron.
Fascinating.
Ron had been sentenced to three years in
prison for grievous bodily harm.
Near the end of his
sentence, he was certified
insane and remanded to a
mental hospital.
What was wanting was a
friendly psychiatrist.
Roger, when you say you want
me to raspberry this man...
I'm not sure of your vernacular.
What do you mean?
Raspberry ripple. Cripple.-
You want to cripple someone.
Yup.
That's right- And why is that?
Because, doctor, I'm afraid
he may not be inclined...
to provide a favorable evaluation to
my employer. And who is your employer?
Ronnie Kray.
Is there hope, Doctor?
Excuse me a moment.
Take your time.
Ronald Kray possesses
possibly the soundest mind
I've seen in 26 years in
psychiatric practice.
In my view, to keep him here would
be a waste of public resources.
A lifetime's integrity down the toilet.
The Queen would survive,
but God save the rest of us.
Mr. Kray?
I hope you know what you're doing.
Yeah, I know what I'm doing. I'm
going back to London. I'm going
to take the... take the car...
Your brother has no real idea who or what
he is. Nor does he trust his own senses.
I've never seen a man
so desperately in need of reassurance.
We all like a nice little
compliment now and again, don't we?
Your brother is arbitrary,
violent and a psychopath.
Alright. Probably
paranoid schizophrenic.
What I'm trying to tell you is
that he's off his fucking rocker.
It's called Stemetil. You need
to give it to your brother
twice a day, or there's going
to be serious trouble.
Oy Frances, the car is outside.
Oh, heh, You've got glamour, Frances.
You're like an East End starlet.
East End harlot's more like it.
They're trousers, mum.
She doesn't look like a harlot.
What she's wearing doesn't matter.
When people see her with Reggie Kray,
they'll think she's a tart.
Why would you say that? He's a gangster,
Frances. The Krays are gangsters.
Well, I think he's sweet.
Oh, God.
And I'm going to kiss him, you hear me?
Hello.
You look lovely.
And so do you.
Hello. This is Big Pat. Hello, Bit Pat!
Reggie.
How are you doing, you all right, mate?
You all right? Nice to see you.
Big Pat's here to keep the riffraff out.
Always. So how come you're
letting us in, then, mate?
Have a good night.Thanks.
Thanks, mate. Cheers.
Oh hello, here's trouble. Hold the phone.
Who are you?
How you doing, big man?- All right, boss?
Are you well?
Yeah, I'm fame... I'm fame...
Are you behaving yourself?
Always.
I'm a teddy bear, me.
Go easy.
If he gives you any trouble, come and
speak to me Come. Y'alright, mum
Yeah, I'm good. She's good.- Hello, Reg.
Everybody here knows you.
Yeah, well, I own it. It's my club.
You mean it's your local?
No, I own the place. It's mine.
I've been by here ten times.
I never knew it was yours.
Well, you can get away with a lot in life
if you, uh... keep your mouth shut.
That's Teddy Anderson, now.
Hi, Teddy. You doing alright? Good to
see you. How's the family? Excellent.
What?
Those men are frightening.
No, no. They're just East End boxers.
They're
lovely. I let 'em drink
in here for free, y'know.
Reggie, that's Joan Collins.
Yeah, it might be, yeah. We had
that... that... Barbara Windsor
in here the other night.
Really? Yeah, she comes in here
quite a bit actually. She loves it.
And uh... That's my... my formula.
What I like to do is I like
to mix celebrities with a few,
just a few, East End villains.
Y'know, punters, they love it. It's really
good for business. Would you like a seat?
Excuse me, Reg. Do you, uh, got a moment?
No, I don't. That's it. I'm busy. Alright?
This is important, Reg.
And this is important as well, Reg.
Alright, alright. Frances,
would you mind if I,
uh, take care of some
business just for a moment?
No, of course not.
Excuse me. I'll be right back.
Sit with her.
What is it?
It's back here.
What?
I'm a firm believer in
the fact if you don't
know, you don't fucking know.
Know what I mean?
Reggie.
How are you, Reg?
Well, I'm alright, I can't complain.
Who'd fucking listen?
What is the palaver? Sit down, Reg.
Sit down, please.
Alright.- You had a question
about the taking of the
purple heart business.
Yeah. The pill game... Go on.
Jack here would like to explain himself.
Go on.
Go on, Jack. Tell Reggie what you told me.
Well, Reg...
Yeah?
I, uh... thing is, under normal
circumstances... my accountants...
Are you gonna take all fucking night, mate?
Cos I've got things to do.
Tell him, Jack.
Go on, spit it out.
I borrowed a few quid off the top.
Right, alright.
I swallowed a few pills on the side.-
Yeah, there's a simple answer.
Things have been a bit... tight at home
And I was... was just trying to keep the
wife happy.- Trying to keep the wife happy.
Is this what you brought me in here? For
this?- It's important.- This nonsense.
It's important business.
It's important, is it? Yeah.
You should know about this. Right,
alright Let's deal with this business.
Alright, tomorrow you
come back to work, yeah?
And you pay back every
fucking penny you owe.
Do you understand?
I was gonna suggest that.
Good. Right. Are we done? Everybody happy?
Alright then. Can I get
back to my fucking evening?
Thank you. Thank you very much, Albie.
Cheers.
Sorry for wasting your time, Jack.
Thanks.
Thanks for coming in. Here you go, mate.
Good?
Fucking, thieving cunt. You understand...
Get him a tissue.
With me? Yeah? Next time I'll
finish you off, you little slag.
Get him out of here. Go
on, Fuck him off. Fuck!
Are you fucking off. What did you say?
Don't you swear in my club.
Get him out of here right now.
Don't swear in my club, you wanker.
Now listen, there's something else.
No, there isn't something else,
alright, cos I've got a young lady
in here, and I'm entertaining.
Yeah, but this is...
Lookit.
See that, there? I see
it. I'm entertaining.
Alright? So I'm gonna have
an evening to myself.
This is important business.
Can't be. My business, innit?
It's my business. I would know.
G'night, Albie.
Hello. Did I miss anything important?
No, just me.
That? That is important.
Is it?
Very important.
Thank you.
Fuck off!
So uh, your brother told me that you uh...
you're going to college.
Right? To... to study... to be a secretary.
Is that right?
Yeah, anything to get out of the East End.
Oh, what's so bad with the East End?
I've just got bigger dreams than pushing
pram or having it with the butcher.
I just don't quite know what they are yet.
East End is not that bad.
The center of the earth
could be anywhere you like.
Even here?
Yeah, even here.
In Bethnal Green?
Yeah, in Bethnal Green.
Do you like being a gangster?
I'm not a gangster.
I'm a club owner.
I like the money and I like the
respect of being a club owner.
I'm not a gangster.
I could've been a boxer,
y'know, but then ya... hello, mate.
I'd end up looking like
some sort of potato and I
wouldn't even know what
day of the week it was.
This way at least I know who I am.
I also know that I've made a
little bit of something of myself.
I don't owe the world anything.
So long as the world agrees with you.
I think the world will be alright.
We shall fight on the beaches
. We shall fight on the landing grounds.
We shall fight in the fields
and in the streets.
We shall fight in the hills. We shall
never surrender. And if...
Ronnie.
Ronnie, come on out.
You've got visitors, mate.
Watch your step, it's a bit wet.
Cor, you alright?
Mmm hmm.
You must be Frances.
Hi.
Yeah?
Hello, Frances. Hello. Welcome
to the family. Well, that
is a bit premature, though, isn't it?
*laughs nervously*
Hey, you don't have a
beer that I can have, do
ya, Ron?
Yeah, of course I do, help yourself.
Right. Don't mind if I have a beer, do ya?
I'll let you get to know each other.
Want a cup of tea? I just put a kettle on.
Take a seat. Go on.
Sit down anywhere you like.
Ey, needs a bit of warming up. So.
What do you think?
Do you think that we look alike?
Me and Reggie?- Oh yes, certainly.
No you don't. You think that he's beautiful
and I've got a face like a gorilla's ass.
No. - It's alright, don't worry about it.
I'm used to it.
Stop doing your hair, right.
Get your stuff out
of the car. Do something
fucking useful.
Go on, go away.
I'm a homosexual, Frances.
Well, ya know, I am uh,
y'know... I'm a giver.
Alright? I'm not a receiver.
There is a difference.
I'm not a faggot.
But I do believe that, y'know, you
should not hide what you are.
Ya shouldn't hide what you
are, because it makes
you very... very sad, y'know?
Make you very sad.
Make you very unwell.
I agree completely. Mmm hmm.
You know me and my brother?
We're gonna rule London.
The Kray's main rivals were the
Richardsons of South London.
They were called the Torture Gang.
For the benefit of the jury...
On whose behalf were you operating
on this side of the river?
Come on, Charlie. Please, I'm
begging you... Oh, no no no no.
You do business with the
court as an entity,
therefore address the
court.- What?- What?
Your honor.
Fuck!
You say 'Your Honor'. By saying Your
Honor, you gain the court's attention...
and open up a channel of communication.
A conduit.
So, we'll try again.
For the benefit of the
jury: On whose behalf
were you working on
this side of the river?
Please, Charlie. I fucking beg you...
Order! Order in this, my court.
Oh, fuck!
You're in Indian Country, old son.
That's what them Cockneys call
south of the river, innit?
Indian Country.
Well? What you doing on my
reservation without my say-so...
filling up your canteen from
my fucking watering hole?
You ain't got the balls to
do that on your own, son.
Who do you work for?
I don't know what you're on about,
Charlie. I don't know what
you're on about... Charlie!
Say it. Say the name.
Say it!
Buzz him.
Objection, Your Honor.
My client is an upstanding citizen.
Objection overruled on
the grounds it's boring.
Oh well, fuck him.
Say it.
Say the Krays, you daft cunt.
No, no. No leading the witnesses!
Fuck off!
Alexander might have been
great, but he wasn't Greek.
No?
No, he was a Macedonian.
But he loved them, though.
Aristotle and that lot. He
was deeply impressed by them
flash Hellenistic cunts.
Kristos, get us some more
of that awful Retsina.
Charlie, we've got to fucking sort this.
You're absolutely right.
Kristos, where is my Retsina?
The Richardsons sent George Cornell
to call for a truce.
All they were saying was:
"Give peace a chance".
Fucking Frank 'll 'ing.
Oh, fuck. Are you out of your bravery
jacket? We're here to parlay.
I will fucking map you up, southie.
Oh no, no, Gordon. Let him
in, he's only little.
Things have got out of hand.
Charlie wants to meet.
Pig and Whistle. Neutral ground.
Just him, you two and Eddie.
Yup? And how do we know
that we're gonna be safe?
Well... that's a little thing
called trust, ain't it?
Trust, eh? You always got one bloke...
harping on about trust, don't you?
But then ya look over your shoulder, right?
And you see there's
another bloke there, right? There
with his hampton in his hand...
and he's preparing to shove
his cock right up your ass.
Well, you wouldn't mind, eh?
You fag puff.
Well, no. No no no no no. Right,
you, get him out of here.
Go on, fuck off. One hour...
and we'll be with ya.
I said bye bye.- Fuck off, John.
There's the door, go on.
Bye bye.- Take that fox with ya, go on.
Get out, ya prick.
A fucking limited.
Hey Charlie, please can I have another egg?
I've eaten this one.
I don't like it, Reggie.
Nah, it's alright. I know
them and I know their pub.
We'll be alright.
Man, you've got to clean that
fucking toilet, mate. It stinks!
Who am I gonna pay to do it?
Some mofo when she
don't? What are you
having to drink?- Ummm...
Forget it, they just walked in.
Hello, mate. Can I get two
Guinnesses, please? Yeah,
hang on a sec, just gotta go
down to change the barrel.
Reg? Ron? The Richardsons were unexpectedly
engaged, so we're gonna look after you.
Oh, it's alright .. yeah, the landlord is
gonna change the barrel for me, thanks.
You don't mind if I pour
myself a pint, yeah?
What is that? Yeah, what you think, puff?
It's a fuckin' tool.
No, it's not. It's a fuckin' rolling pin.
Who are you? Fanny Cradock?
What are you doing with that? Are
you going to bake me a cake?
Gonna sing me a song and watch
me blow out me fucking candles?
I come here for a fucking shootout, right?
A proper shootout with some proper men.
Like Colonel Custer and Geronimo.
Have you ever heard of them? No.
Because you were too in your penny
baking fucking fairy cakes weren't ya?
Reg, this lot is a bunch of fucking
nonces to a man. They're fucking nonces.
Get out of me fucking way.
Go on, get out. Go on,
fuck off. You call yourself
a fucking gangster?
A shootout, right? Is a fucking shootout!
Like a Western.
Wankers! Fucking embarrassing. Waste
of my time. Fucking waste of time.
Well, your brother has done a runner.
Nah, he's
just genuinely disappointed
with you, that's all.
Look at that, it's full
of iron, that is. It
takes a while, that
does, yeah, to settle.
Well, Charlie Richardson said we're
to knock the granny out of you, Reg.
Oh yeah, he did, did he? That's
good of him. Right, listen.
When you see him next, you
tell him for me, yeah, that I say:
Fuck Charlie, right? And
fuck his brother, yeah?
And fuck that fat Georgie Cornell
that hangs out with him.
Fuck your face, yeah? Yeah?
And fuck the fucking lot of you as well.
What do you think of that, ey?
You like that?- mmm.
You won't mind if I fight back, will ya?
If you think you can manage it.
Nah, it's more for me pride,
really, to be honest.
I warn you. I'm not gonna
fight fair, though.
That's why I brought these.
Alright.
Now before we start, I've got a little
joke for you? You're gonna love this one.
Paranoid schizophrenic
who walks into a bar...
You fuckers...
They never stood a chance against
my beautiful Reggie.
A gang war seemed certain.
Fucking hell, Ron.
But on the day of the World Cup final,
Scotland Yard had its say as well.
There's Ball, running himself daft.
Goooaaal! Get in there, you cunts!
Police, stay right where you are.
Oh, come on,
boys... not today.
What you mean, no goal?
Wait.
Wait wait wait. Wait!
It's a goal. It's a goal! It's
a fucking goal! It's a goal!
Charlie Richardson was
sentenced to 25 years
for fraud, extortion and assault.
London was an open city
and the Krays moved in.
Glad you could come, Mr. De Faye.
Mr. Payne.
I'm not often intrigued,
but your message...
it intrigued.- mmmm.
Sit down.
These are the Kray twins.
Ronald and Reginald.
Yes, I've, uh... heard of them.
You'll find them useful friends.
What is this about, Mr. Payne?
This is about a gambling
casino in Knightsbridge
called Esmeralda's Barn.
I'm not familiar with it.
Really?
Well you'll be shocked
to learn that you earned
24,000 pounds from it in
the last three months.
My friends and I would
like to purchase it from
you. We have the contract
ready for your signature.
Ruling London involved intelligence
and intimidation.
It's not for sale.
You might find that in the future
there is a less polite approach.
The trick was to cultivate
a quiet certainty that
should it be needed violence
was on offer...
Yeah...- , and would be happily applied.
Leslie Payne was a fronter and a fixer.
Reggie found Payne useful,
but Ron was suspicious of him.
Afraid his scams were the opposite
of what a gangster should be.
Consider Las Vegas.
Right.
It is all legal and all run by the mafia.
Soon, London will be the same. What with
Havana gone, the mafia is moving in.
Meyer Lansky has already made inquiries.
Meyer Lansky? Yeah.
As in the Meyer Lansky?
Meyer Lansky.
What, the Americans gonna try muscling us?
Nah, they don't work that way.
They don't want a war, Ron.
They're businessmen.
Well, maybe I want a war, anyway.
Now look, what they do want is to know
who is the up and coming local firm.
Cos they will colonize London by financing
that firm and franchising the city.
So you have to prove to the Americans
that the Krays are the only gang in town.
Yeah, very fucking interesting.
The world could be our oyster.
Payne. What?
You say "our" a lot, right?
You say 'our' and you also so 'we' a lot.
Do I?
My question is... is your last name Kray?
Listen, Ron. You keep the pearls.
I'm perfectly happy with the soft bits.
Yeah, I bet you are. I bet you are.
Reggie, I say it's a very bad idea, this.
It's a bad idea.
I say, right, that we meet these mafioso
scum at London in a pub, right.
We pick them up, we chop them up.
We put them in their
fucking luggage and send
em straight home away.
That's the plan.
Well, I'm glad we could have this meeting.
Mr. Lansky has taken an interest
in the Colony Sporting Club.
He has his casino people there right now.
Well, Mr. Lansky might want to know that
we happen to have a casino of our own.
Really? Your own casino?
Well, you see, we own Las Vegas.
But here the Atlantic Ocean is in our way.
So Mr. Lansky lacks
the ability to, uh,
ensure the physical
security of his property.
From both outside muscle... and the cops.
He thinks the Kray family can help. London
is going to be the Las Vegas of Europe.
We need someone to front and
someone to muscle for us.
I mean, y'know, we can do
your security, that's not
a problem. Y'know, but we
don't wanna work for ya.
We'd much rather that we work with ya.
What Reggie's trying to say...
I think he
knows what he's trying to say.
He just said it.
We're in your backyard.- Yeah.- Mr. Lansky
is open to discussions of this nature.
He sends this as goodwill gesture. Just
a taste. For expenses. Open it, please.
Now, the second briefcase contains business
of my own I need to take care of. Please.
Bearer bonds. Free money.
A hundred grand in negotiable bearer
bonds jacked from a bank in Montreal.
Too hot to move in North America.
It's a hundred grand.
Could you guys handle that?
Yeah, we can handle it.
Really? Good.
Boys who jacked it get 20%.
We split the rest 60/40.
If this works out, Reggie, I got a two
million dollar backlog of those scharols.
Does that sound like you're
staying out of our way?
50/50, mate.
I like you, Reggie.
50/50 it is. Done.
I'm glad that we could make a
deal.- Yeah.- Now this feels right.
Listen, uh, you come to
Philadelphia anytime...
you see what you want, any size, any
shape, right? We'll get it for ya.
A nice Italian girl. A little
spaghetti and meatballs.
I prefer boys.
Excuse me? I didn't catch that.
I said I prefer boys.
Italians, actually.
Sometimes Greek, but I'm
not prejudiced. No.
Because I happened to
have a Negro, once.
And a Tahitian who I bent up like a
pretzel. I really fucking hurt him.
You've got a lot of fucking
balls to admit that, kid. You
know what, you've got some set
of fucking gestantes on you.
You know what I say to that?
Bravo a salute.
C'mon. Salute. Huh?
Am I right, fellas?
What fucking balls. Salute.
Cheers, mate. Cheers.
Well done.
Cheers, mate.
You don't understand.
He's not what you think he is, alright?
He is really sweet
and it is exciting to be with him.
Just because you have a boring life
doesn't mean I have to as well.
If I have a boring life, it's
because I gave up my life for you.
Oh, Frankie, you take my breath away.
You can have mine.
You're a joker. Go on, get in the car.
Hurry up.
Esmeralda's Barn made
money like a dream. Two
thousand pounds a week pure profit.
There was nothing to do but enjoy it.
Owning that casino meant
everything to Reggie.
He'd finally crossed the
line between the old East
End and the green pastures
of the Golden West.
He was becoming a celebrity himself.
As long as their health
didn't suffer, the high
rollers loved rubbing elbows
with gangsters.
Aristocrats and criminals
have a lot in common.
They're both selfish, get
bored easily...
and have access to wads of cash they
didn't have to work honestly to get.
The topper? Neither have any interest
in bourgeois rules or morality.
Put it all together
with a roulette wheel .
A stunning recipe for success.
Ron was the odd man out.
His pills stabilized him,
but they'd never cure him.
Clubland held little charm...
and he yearned for Reggie
and the dark side of gangland.
As soon as you turn your back...
life plays dirty tricks on ya, y'know?
We wouldn't spend Christmas
together that year.
There was an old warrant on Reggie.
The last six months of his sentence was
on appeal, but it was denied.
He was to surrender in the morning.
My real life was about to begin.
See you in a bit.
See ya later, Reg.
So long, Reg.
Frank.
Will you look after your sister while
I'm away? I will, Reg. Yeah?- Yeah.
Good lad.
Move it, Kray.
Stop on the line.
You're nothing in here.
Fuck him.
Fuck him up.
Leave him alone, Gibbsy.
Bury him, Reggie .
Shut up, all of ya.
Come on, Reg.
Don't let them do you like this .
You're not so tough now, are ya, eh?
Give that bastard some back.
You're nothing in here.
Nothing. - please, no more, governor.
No more, please.
That's more like it, Reggie.
Please?
A little respect doesn't hurt, does it?
No more.
I have shit bigger turds.
Please, water.
You want some water?
Look at that, gents. He's only
begging for water. Fuck off, PT
What do you think of him now, your
famous Reggie fucking Kray? Fuck you!
Begging for fucking water.
What has he come to.
Here you are, Reg. Now don't spill it.
Cos you've had a little tumble, ain't ya?
Hey?
Good boy.
Water?- Look.- Fucking cockhead.
Fuck off.- Look who
it is. Reggie Kray, begging
for fucking... water.
Reggie... Reggie... Reggie
Hello, Frances.
Hello, Ron.
I've saw Reg today.
He sends his best. He
says it's probably best
that you don't go visit
him this year, alright?
Did he say why?
No, he didn't mention it.
Did you know that it is
possible, right, for a
person to become a ghost
while they're still alive?
Do you think so?
Well it's happened to you, innit?
No no no, listen.
No, what?
No no no, please please please.
Just for a moment. Just listen.
Gambling clubs are legally obliged
to pay winnings on the spot.
And that is why we insist
our gamblers pay their
debts on the spot as well.
It's very simple.
Yes, I know. I've heard
you, but that's your
problem, right? That's
your problem and not mine.
Mine is that I want fifty thousand pounds.
Oh, here you go again with your fifty
thousand pounds to go to Nigeria.
It is not just to go to Nigeria, is it?
I want to set up a company.
Right? I want to build a city
in Nigeria for the children.
Near Enugu.
Enugu. Yes, Enugu.
Yes, Enugu. I told you, Enugu, right?
You don't know everything, do you, Payne?
Did you know that "Enugu"
is the African word for 'Utopia'?
No.
No you did not.
Did you know that 'Utopia' is
the Greek word for 'nowhere'?
For fifty thousand pounds I
can make that 'somewhere'.
I can turn it into a place where people
will smile at me and children will dance.
I will smile for you, Ron.
I will smile for you if you tell me
where I can get fifty thousand pounds.
I'm telling you, I'm fucking telling
you... just put it out of the casino.
I cannot put it out of the
casino that's what I'm
saying.
Put it out of the casino, you cunt.
Despite the temptation. Do
not meddle with a foolproof
way of making the money.
I am not a fucking banker.
No no no!- I am not a fucking banker.
Great! Genius.
Look at that. That has made
it all the more mendable.
This is a man who wants to build a city.
Don't you fucking threaten me, you cunt.
Don't you fucking dare
talk to me like that, you cunt.
Reggie is not here now, alright?
He's fucking gone, isn't he?
So you work for me, Ron Kray.
So you will trotter on
down to the fucking bank
and you will fetch me my
fifty thousand pounds.
Yeah, I'll go to the bank and have a
little talk to them and see what I can do.
And I'll tell you. I
may work for you, Ron,
but I'm certainly not
afraid of you, alright?
Well that is fucking stupid as well,
because you fucking should be.
Because if my brother hadn't of vouched
for you, you'd be fucking dead.
What happened?
What are you doing here? Didn't
Ronnie tell you not to come?
I missed you.
Yeah.
Frankie, I don't want you to come here
and see me like this. Do you understand?
Who did it?
What?
Your face.
Was it one of the other prisoners?
No. No, it was one of the guards, alright?
Have you reported them?
No.
But y'know what? When I get out, I'm thinking,
right, I might roll down to the ol' houses
of parliment and have a word with the prime
minister. Because he will listen. He will.
Frankie, this is prison.
OK? That's what it is, is.
The law of the jungle in here.
But don't worry about it because
I'm a big boy and I can
look after meself. And I'll
be out very soon, alright?
Go on and look at that lump over there.
You see him? With the big hat.
There's a very good reason why we
all call him handbag. Alright?
I don't want a life like this.
Just waiting for you while you're
in prison. I know. I know, right.
Frankie, it won't happen again.
How can you be sure?
Because I know.
Because I promise you that it won't happen again. Alright?
I know how you can know be sure.
Go on.
You could go straight.
Be a casino owner. Club owner.
You enjoy it.
Just forget everything else.
It really is that simple for you, innit?
Just "go straight?"
Babe, Life isn't always the
way we want it to be, y'know?
Life has other plans. It's
the way it is, it's life.
I love you.
I've never loved anybody before,
but I love you, Reggie.
And I love you too.
Do you think it can protect people?
What?
Love.
I like him. Yeah, he's got
something about him, doesn't he?
You know what I reckon it is?
- What? I think it's his hips.
- Yeah.
I want to blow the soul out of that horn.
You feeling a bit horny, are you, Ron?
I am. I am.
Go on, do it. I will. Do it. I want
to blow the soul out of that horn.
I am going to do it.
Bugger you, Tiger.
That's it, Ron. Give it a fucking blow.
Kill it.
Oh, fucking hell. Right.
Hello? Hello?
Yes, Ron, Hello.
You know when I plan
to die?
When, Ron?
In the very last minute.
Don't fucking encourage
him, for fuck's sake.
Look at you, you flash fuckers, alright?
Now I may not be very good,
right, but a good gangster?
Oh yeah. I'll fucking claim that title.
And how many titles could you claim? Hey?
Superficial light.
Oh yeah?
Dripping in your synthetic opulates.
Ha. It's disgusting, really it is.
Yeah.
Right. A bit of magic. You love magic,
don't you? All kids love magic.
You might all be aware that there are
three magic 'C's in the word Carpacia.
But how many C's...
are there in the word cunt?
Just you.
You're free.
What are you doing throwing
stones at the window?
They're not stones. These
are Lemon Sherberts.
Here you go.
Oh, well played!
Why don't you ring the bell?
Well, your mum. I mean.
I'm not being funny here,
but the thought of your
mum answering that door
is a bit shocking, so.
I thought she'd give me grief
on account of where I've been.
You mean prison?
Yeah, prison. You look beautiful.
You look beautiful too.
I know it's a bit late, alright,
but I've got your Christmas present here.
Do you want me to throw it up?
No.
Well, do you want me to deliver it?
I ain't going through that door.
Alright.
You cheeky bugger.
Be careful.
Bit late now, innit?
Right. Your flowers.
Thank you.
And...
your Christmas present.
Sorry it's late.
Go on. Open it.
Frances Shea, will you marry me?
We live free and above board?
On my honor.
Yes, Reggie Kray, I will marry you.
That weren't mine!
Cheeky.
Bastard!
C'mon, show us your fucking hoochie!
Give us a fucking
look.- You're not listening.
You're not listening.
All I'm saying... All I'm saying
is crime is still a business.
You need a public relations department
and we've got Joseph Goebbels.
Is he the fat one?
You read lips.
What's he saying? What's he saying, Les?
Oh, stroke him off. I think he's saying
something about Gobbles... or nobles
That's very strange.
He ain't happy.
You'll see.
Nice, innit?
Oh, he looks lovely, Ron. Yeah, he's put
on a little bit of "timboo", innit he?
He's going to be very, very upset.
Did I miss something?
Is this not... this is Friday night, right?
Well, I tried to tell you.
Yeah, but it's Friday
night, right? You
didn't tell me that it
was this bad, did you?
It's Ron, innit? He's run the
place into the ground. He's
turned a straight money
earner into a financial wreck
And I'll tell you one other thing...
this place
will crash when we get
our tax bill next week.
What's he saying?
Go on, what's he saying?
He's just told him that you're missing
tax payments. The silly cunt.
Let's go.
Right, listen. It's still an
honest business, you understand?
How very rude.
Hey! Where are you going?
This is fucking criminal mate
Oh, there he is. My
beautiful brother, Reggie.
A toast to my beautiful brother.
Home at last, like Agamemnon returned
to Ithaca.
And beautiful Frances, where have you been?
It's as if you've returned from the dead.
What are you doing, mate?
What are you fucking playing at? Hey?
I'm not playing at anything, am I?
It's you. You
come in here, You don't
even say "Hello, Ron."
You don't even have a drink.
You just bugger off. What's
that about?
All right. Hello, Ron. Cheers, mate.
Fuck you!
What are you shouting at me, for?
Because you, right? You had the
world on a string, yeah...
but you couldn't hold it
together, so you fucked it up.
Don't... uh, listen, you was away.
I was in prison. I was in prison!
So I had to make do with what I had.
Are you going Ron or Reg?
Score?
Mmm hmm.
Reginald. He'll never go
down in front of the missus.
You had everything, mate. You had it all.
You are... I didn't have you, right.
Unbelievable.- Reggie.- It's all
right, honestly. I've got this. It's fine.
Yeah, actually, he's got this.
Thank you very much. He's
a big boy. We're talking about
earning a living. Y'know?
We're talking about being
gangsters, right, which
is what we are. So you
can just fuck off...
Go on.
Don't.
Y'know, one of these days, Ron Kray, your
miserable life will swallow you whole.
Yeah, well you should know all
about it, actually, y'know,
because I have heard all the stories.
They're not good...
Your mum did palm us off
with the damaged goods,
didn't she? And you're very,
very damaged, aren't you?
Alright, just get in the car. Don't you
ever speak to Frances like that again.
That's right, Frances. Blood
is thicker than water,
y'know? And I've been with
Reggie since the womb.
Ron, shut up. I want you to apologize to
Frances right now.
Right... right. All right, Frances.
I'm sorry, alright?
Yes. I'm truly very sorry. The club is
very, very empty. A bit like you, really.
There is fuck all in it,
apart my brother's cock.
You, alright, are a fucking disgrace, mate.
You hit me.
Yeah.
No...
No, Ron.
No... no.
Now you've done it, you fucking cunt.
Fucking cunt.
For fuck's sake. Not the bottle.
Not the bottle, you...
No! Not the balls.
Fucking cunt! Wanker!
Sweetheart, please leave.
Fucking... Fucking cunt!
Give me that.
Never mess with a man's jewels, mate.
Now, what are you doing?
No, Ron. No, no. No,
no. That is a bottle, Ron.
That bottle...
I'm gonna split 'em up. Just a minute,
you fucking sit down, you shit.
They're family. Save it. Get
out of the fucking way.
Put it down.
It's gone too far.
Now, I told you.
Now, c'mon, that's enough.
No.
Enough, Reg, mate.
You just don't understand.
Fuh... Fuck.
You don't understand me.
Well, that's probably because
I don't want to fucking
understand you right now Ron.
I just wanted to just, y'know...
There's no point in fucking explaining.
It's fucking hopeless. Go on. Help me up.
Help me up. That really fucking hurt.
What are you doing? For fuck's sake, Ron.
What I'm trying to tell you is
very simple, right? Listen.
I am very, very...
very fragile myself, alright?
Yup, fragile, I've got it.
Very fragile.
I've got it!
Alright, c'mon now, for fuck's sake.
I'm not myself.
This isn't me, is it?
This isn't us. None of this is us.
I am very sorry.
It's OK.
Are you done?
Is she gone?
Yes, she's gone.
She's a keeper.
Gee, thanks, Ron.
Thanks.
There she is.
Yup, I've got her.
Alright, stop here.
That girl's gonna be the death of me.
Go on, there ya go.
Frankie. Frank.
Excuse me, sorry.
I need to have a word with you about
something. I don't care if you forget me.
Don't say that.
It's true.
You don't mean it. Don't tell me
what I mean. I know what I mean.
Come on... Come on, Frances.
Can't we just start again?
Right? From the beginning,
y'know, right? We can
get rid of everything
that's bad, right...
and we'll just keep everything that's good.
What about Ron?
Well he's not exactly a good bit, is he?
Well,
eh, I mean he's not exactly
a bad bit, either.
Y'know?- He was awful to me yesterday.
Yeah,
yeah he was, but y'know that's...
that's Ron.
If he don't take his tablets, he is,
he is, he's like, he is a nightmare.
He is not always like that, y'know?
He's got a heart of gold.
He loves you bits, he
thinks the world of you.
Honestly, when you left, he was in pieces.
He was like: "Where did she go?"
I said, "She's left."
"Well you better get
after here, cos she's a keeper."
You are a keeper. So he's right. He said
Tell her I'm very sorry.
He is sorry, and I'm sorry.
We're all sorry.
But you know what?
That's what happens sometimes.
Families are stupid, aren't they?
They fight... they make up...
they... they... they stick together
because they love each other.
That's what they do.
Don't tell me about
forgetting you, alright,
because that ain't
happening either.
Y'know, I spent the last six months
thinking about nothing but you.
So I get out and the club's got me a...
Alright.
I'm sorry.
It was time for the Krays to enter the
secret history of the 1960's.
As absurd as it seems...
it grew out of Ron's nutter dream of
building a utopian city in Nigeria.
Some are born to be Ronnie Kray...
and some have Ronnie Kray thrust upon them.
Lord Boothby was a distinguished
member of the House of Lords.
Ronnie.
Yes?
I regret that my answer is no.
Nigeria is simply too far away...
and I never involve myself in a
thing I can't control personally.
I'm so sorry.
He's really lovely, isn't he?
I take it you like ice
and a slice, my lord?
Ice and a slice.
Please, Teddy bear.
And don't spare the horses.
Do you know where I hear that lemons
are particularly lovely and fresh?
No, where?
Enugu... Nigeria.
You're very well informed, Teddy.
Very well informed.
Down the hatch.
Do you like it down the hatch, Teddy?
Boothby declined,
but friendship ensued.
And the perverted Peer was soon a guest
at Ron's flat.
The ripples would spread far and wide.
Do call me later, Tom.
Harry, all alone?
No need to be. There is
plenty of fruit on the tree.
Tom, not in the House of Commons tonight?
Yeah.
Fucking look at me, you cunt.
Yeah?
Go on. Fucking look at him now.
Fucking look at me.
Look at me.
Good lord, that's Bob Boothby.
Yes, Prime Minister, sir.
At an orgy!
The tories are going to have
trouble explaining this.
Here, sir.
Is that Tom Driberg?
In fact, yes, sir.
There is no moral advantage to my party
if my party are also involved.
It gets a bit stickier, sir.
Where were these photos taken?
Cazenove Road, Hackney.
What in god's boots
were they doing in
Hackney?
Well that's where it gets sticky.
I thought the orgy was the sticky bit...
it gets stickier still?
We've had two brothers,
gangsters, under surveillance.
The Krays.
The photographs were taken
in Ronald Kray's flat.
Orgies aside, we're tracking
fraud, protection rackets...
And the American mafia
might also be involved.
London's bottom had reached her top.
Scandal loomed.
The elections are in ten weeks.
They'll vote out both sides of the house.
What exactly are you doing about it?
Bugger all, by the looks of it.
Is that Italian?
I don't know.
Is it a Daimler?
It's nice, that is.
Oh, what do you want for Christmas?
Umm, I don't know. You
don't have to get me
anything.- Ey?- You don't
have to get me a present.
Oh, that is ridiculous.
Not get you anything for Christmas?
Alright, well you surprise me then.
I'll give you a sack of coal.
I'll get you a sockful of coal.
Lucky thing.
Well, what about that?
What about it?
For Christmas.
For me?
That's going to be my club.
Is it?
Yeah.
West End, a touch of class.
That is our ticket out of here.
It's snowing.
Yeah.
Gone.
What did I want for Christmas?
My Reggie, free and above board.
But Ron wanted his Reggie back as well.
He longed for his gangster twin.
And Reggie... he chose the
HIDE-A-WAY instead.
The owner was Hugh McCowan, the
son of a baronet.
Though he was not usually intimidated
by the working classes...
he agreed to sell half the club.
Reggie knew he'd get the rest in time.
A dirty deal for a clean life.
Ron was terrified of
Reggie leaving him behind.
He sent Mad Teddy round to kill the deal.
Listen, gentlemen...
I've spoken to Reggie
I'm sorry...
I can't look at you, darling, or I'm
going to get lost in your eyes.
I've got a deal with Reggie...
This is shit.
I signed a contract.
I have an arrangement with Reggie, ask him.
Crap.
Gentlemen, please.
Please, I have customers.
Out of the way. That's it, come on.
I have customers here, gentlemen, please.
I have spoken to Reggie.
We don't work for Reggie.
We work for Ronnie.
Ron almost got what he wanted.
McCowan backed out of the deal,
but he also called the police.
Reggie and Ron were both charged
with extortion.
Frannie, I'm tell you, the
police stitched me up.
I am innocent.
I'm...
completely innocent.
Even if you are...
What?
You're back in prison.
You made a promise to me.
And it still stands.
I'm fucking innocent!
Sorry, I don't mean to
swear at you, alright?
I really want you to marry me.
Please.
If you're innocent and acquitted,
I'll marry you.
If you're guilty, I never want to
see you again. Why do you say that?
Frankie, don't...
Frankie, don't.
Strangely, it was Lord Boothby
who saved the day.
His walk on the wild side
had not gone unnoticed.
I've finally found the photo.
It's been forwarded to the proper places.
Say: "Enugu".
Enugu.
The photograph taken in Boothby's
flat ended up with the paper.
Along with the story of
sexual misconduct...
between a gangster and the
member of the House of Lords.
The problem is Arnold,
that, unfortunately...
It's all true for once.
I don't care about the truth, Harold.
Except that, the greater the truth...
the greater the libel.
An election was looming.
But the Prime Minister brought in his
fixer, Arnold Goodman to sort things out.
Get me Cecil King at the Sunday Mirror.
The great and the good engineered
a cover-up. A cracking good one.
When the Kray's defense threatened to call
Boothby as a character witness...
the implication was clear.
The government would have
to drop its case...
or face the consequences.
It was this that made the Krays
the untouchables of London crime.
New information casts poor light on
the prosecution witness, Mr. McCowan.
Case dismissed.
That night the Kray's held their
celebration party at McCowan's club.
Reggie had bought the
HIDE-A-WAY that same afternoon.
At a discount.
Thank you.
Why are you here, then?
I've come to see the
difference between you and me.
The difference, yeah?
Alright.
What do you know?
I grew up poor...
like you.
I boxed as a lad, like you.
But it didn't turn me into a thief.
But it did turn you into
policing, didn't it?
Yeah.
It did turn you into handing
your own over at the bar, innit?
You know, the difference
between us, right...
apart from, y'know, the obvious...
is that I, right, I work for me.
And you...
You work for them.
Sir, I can explain.
This is Scotland Yard.
And this investigation will end at once.
But there's so much more
that we can get them on...
Your investigation into
the Krays will end at once!
Alright, alright.- She's
wearing black, mate.
I know. I know. She's
read it wrong, isn't she?
She thought it was a fucking funeral.
Wearing black oh that fucking bitch.
I know. Don't drive yourself mad.
Wait'll you see the daughter,
she looks unbelievable in white.
What do you see in her?
I see meself, yeah.
I see what I could be.
Y'know?
If I wasn't so scared.
You're not afraid of anything.
Right.
Well, only meself, y'know.
And you.
Yeah.
What is she doing?
You know what she's going
to be saying, alright?
Just take it easy. Deep breaths.
Why are not you inside, dear?
Are you
absolutely sure you want
to go through with this?
Mom, please, don't start this again.
It's all right, Frank.
I love him.
Love.
Do you even know what love is, Frances?
Well, I know it's not
an answer to anything.
But love is a witness.
Reggie sees me.
And I see him.
And who are you to refuse that?
I'm your mother.
Ey. East End starlet, Frances.
That's you.
Thank you.
Oh, Ron, look at her.
She looks beautiful.
Enjoy yourself.
Gracious God...
accept our prayers for
Frances and Reginald...
that they may reap the
harvest of the Spirit...
and reflect your glory
through Christ Jesus our lord.
Amen.
Amen
Fucking... sing.
We honeymooned in Greece.
The Parthenon had stood for two
thousand, four hundred years.
Reggie's promise to go straight
lasted two weeks.
Two Aces...
New Mill...
the Gigi Club...
and let's not forget Ronnie Scott.
And this is the bearer
bond cash in Hamburg.
The kettle's on the boil.
It is tea.
We started out near Marble
Arch in West London.
But we both missed the East End.
And so we took an empty flat
below Ron's at Cedra Court.
Like all else in life it was
supposed to be temporary.
Not very clever.
Ron's parties would keep me awake at night.
And clubland kept Reggie
out until all hours.
He enjoyed being a gangster, after all.
We heard
that you, uh, were down the
Regency the other night.
Waving a shotgun.
Those bastard Barry brothers
blocked me from coming in.
They said I was drunk.
You were!
You was drunk as a skunk.
Waving a shotgun.
No.
Now you know we look after that place.
Right?
We don't want you messing
around down there.
I spiced the evening up for people, y'know?
Spiced it up.
Here you go.
You're not going to do
that anymore, are you?
No, sir.
Good lad.
Oh, bollocks.
Go on, get up, Jack. Fuck.
This is so kind of you.
Sweet, isn't it?
Lovely, yeah.
Oh, hello.
Oh, uh...
Is that OK??
No, no.
No, Frances, that wo...
that won't do. Umm...
Go and sit with Mr. Kray
and I'll sort it out.
Alright.
She can't even make a decent cup of tea.
Yeah, poor Reggie. ey?
It was a good effort.
She looks like a budgie in
that dress, doesn't she?
You reckon that a man wouldn't pick her
up if she was laying in the gutter.
Yeah.- Oh well.
Poor Reggie. Right, I swear...
I shall flush that.
I left without saying goodbye.
A sad victory.
I'd never be good enough
for their Reggie.
He was Nipper's Reggie as well.
Reed couldn't rest unless he clapped
eyes on my husband once a day.
I often had to settle for the same.
Wherever you're going,
don't stop until you get to the sea.
But we all need something.
What I shared with Ron
was needing pills to get through the day.
Sleeping pills helped sometimes,
other pills helped other times.
They were like a friend who
held no judgment...
and only wanted to be loved
in return.
Mother's little helpers.
They were very well named.
Don't go too fast.
We're not going anywhere like too fast.
We're in the grass.
Alright, almost there.
Alright?
A bit more...
OK?- OK.
You ready?
Yes. Really ready? Yes.
Oh my God.
Do you like it?
Yes, what... what kind is it?
What's it called?
It's uh, it's a Triumph. It's a Spitfire.
Triumph Spitfire. Can I get in?
Yeah, of course you can, it's yours.
Happy Birthday. Here y'are.
Happy Birthday, Frances.
Thank you.
Will you teach me how to drive?
Uhhh, I can.
Now?
Umm... not today.
Why not?
I... uh... just can't... not today.
But I can tomorrow.
Alright.
Sorry.
Kray.
There's an inherent threat
in that one commanding syllable.
It's the only word
some need to hear.
What's that mean? The only word?
Well, you're like Ford.
Oh yeah. Or Shell.
Or Woolworth's.
Woolworth's. Yes, that's... uh...
that's very interesting.
What I'm saying is Kray is a brand...
and an established reputation
means less maintenance, less violence.
Y'know? People fall, actually, into line.
Clubs are asking for our protection
before we even offer it.
Yeah, that's true, actually.
They, uh, yes..
I suppose that would leave us with
less straightening out to do.
He's right.
Makes sense.
See, but I happen to like...
I like straightening out, y'know?
Once in a while...
obliging someone to the old cobbles, ey?
Whats wrong with that?
I just think you could
do better, Ron, y'know.
It will keep you out of prison. I mean,
none of us are getting any younger.
Y'know, you need to leave
this all behind you, I mean.
Y'know, you've got to look to the future,
you and that lovely young wife of yours.
Fairy tales!
That's fucking water.
This is a firm, right? I'm a fucking face.
Are you alright, mate? Can you see?
I'll fucking serve you
up, you fucking cunt.
Fucking bent out of order!
I don't fucking like him.
I don't trust him.
He talks too much, ask
too many questions.
I want him fucking dead.
Leslie Payne, right, is our business, mate,
and you want him dead?
It's... I mean, have
you been taking your
tablets?- Fuck tablets, right?
Bugger tablets.
Bugger Payne, the fucking... pain
in the ass and fuck his briefcase.
I don't give a fuck what's in there. I
want to know what's going on up there.
He knows too much about... things.
Things about us, Reggie.
He knows too many things about us.
He knows too many things about us?
Right, Albie, do you know
things about us, ey?
You know things, ey?
About Ron... about me,
about the firm, right?
You know about... about payments, right?
Do you know that we cash
bearer bonds, yeah?
Do you know we pay off juries to make them
look fucking favorably upon us, do you?
Yes.
You do. There's a fucking surprise. Jack,
mate, do you know anything about fraud?
Anything at all. Take a punt.
Do you know anything about
how we pay off policemen
every fucking final
Thursday of the month.
Do you know that?
Course I do.
Fucking surprise, that. So
why don't we kill Jack, now?
Or we do Albie as well?
We'll do the fucking lot.
Or you can do me and I'll do you,
then we're both fucking dead.
That's a genius idea.
Listen to yourself, Ron.
You're fucking nuts.
People who live in glass houses
shouldn't throw stones.
Did you know I never drank gin
until I came here?
Oh, well next you'll be singing
God Save the Queen, won't ya?
What did you want to have a
word with me about, Mr. Bruno?
Well things are going well,
we're very happy on my side of the pond.
Well that's good. Y'know,
we're very, very happy also.
OK.
Cheers.
Do you realize that I asked
to speak to you alone?
You see, in our line of work...
it is not good to be famous.
Anonymous is the goal.
It's Mr. Lansky, Reg.
He sees a lot of potential in you.
But he sees limitations
in your brother Ron.
Well, yeah. Maybe... maybe...
they could just sit down and
meet each other. Couldn't they?
I mean, he could come across for a chat.
A chat?
You guys crack me up, really.
You ever hear of the Gallo brothers?
From Brooklyn? No.
Similar loose cannon situation.
You see, Ron is your Joey.
And it's not going to end
well in either case.
What exactly are you asking
me to do, Mr. Bruno?
I'm asking you to do something about Ron.
I can't do that.
He's my brother.
OK.
There's nothing I can do.
I ain't finished with you, yet.
Mr. Kray takes care of this warehouse.
Now you say Kray one more time...
and I'm gonna hurt you, you understand?
I have an arrangement with Mr.
Kray. - I
didn't ask you whether
you had an arrangement.
I asked if you understood me.
The Richardson gang were away.
But George Cornell had
crossed the river to work
the protection racket
on their behalf.
I fucking warned you.
Ron's response would secure his place
in gangster legend.
What is that? Is that
English breakfast tea? You
can tell by your face,
Ted, what you think of it.
Lovely box, innit. It is not an
English breakfast, that's not, no.
That's got pheromones in it, that's got.
That's musky.
That's best bit of magic, that is.
That's very beautiful, innit?
I'm glad you like it.
I do... that's... that's proper.
Me mum will be very,
very pleased with that.
Do you have that away from
the old warehouse, did
ya?- Yeah.- Don't say anything,
I mean, it's alright.
Goes to Mrs. Kray.
Thank you.
And the other matter.
Yeah, what matter?
What, that?
Yeah
Right...
I mean, I'm not in the mind
to hand out refunds, am I?
Can't you handle it yourself?
I pay you for protection, Ron.
What are you trying to say?
Nothing... You just said it, didn't you?
You fucking said it.
You come in here with
your fucking nose, right?
And your tea.
Your fucking exotic tea.
Right? And you say that.
I'm not very good at my job.
I didn't mean it like that.
You fucking did.
No, I...
Uh!
I'll tell you what.
This matter of yours...
I'll deal with it for you. Alright?
You go with Teddy, right,
and you bring me two thousand pounds, OK?
And in return, I promise that I
will have George Cornell killed.
Alright?
I didn't say...
I didn't saying anything about
killing, Ron. You fucking did!
You fucking meant it.
Look at you, you meant it with your eyes.
Look at your eyes.
Ey? It's in your fucking eyes.
Are you threatening me?
No.
Cos there is death in your eyes
and you're fucking threatening me.
Is he threatening me?
It's hard to tell, Ron.
I'll pay.
You what?
I'll pay. You will? Yeah.
There it is. And a deal is a deal.
It's done.
Yeah.
It's done. It's over.
Teddy, take him.
Thank you.
Very kind of you...
Thank you -
for the tea.
That's a good deal.
How do I look?
Fucking deadly.
You want me to come in with you?
In there?
Come on.
You'll stay in the car.
Anything you need to tell me?
Well look what the cat dragged in.
Jesus.
Yeah, you're not laughing now, are you?
For fuck's sake.
Boss? The fuck?
Get off the phone.
Shut up, you heard.
What are you fucking looking at?
You didn't see nothing.
That's Ronnie Kray, that is, innit?
Fucking hell.
Reggie.
Are you mad?
The Blind Beggar, yeah? Cornell?
It's on the fucking radio.
Reggie.
Hi, Mum.
Oh, thank you, cheers.
Oh, look at you!
Look how handsome you are.
I'll get you a cup of tea.
Thanks, Mum.
Albie? I'm all right, Violet.
Thank you.
You do look lovely, Reg.
How many witnesses?
Well, it was a quiet night.
Seven.
Seven?
Albert Woods was with Cornell.
Plus five regulars.
I don't know them.
And that barmaid, the blonde? The one
with the big fucking pair of eyes.
Fuck's sake.
And you bring this here? This is where you
bring it? You bring it straight to mums?
Don't moan about it, right? It's done,
innit? What are we going to do? Hmm?
We?
Yeah.
Where's the weapon?
It's here, Reg.
There you go. Now, uh... would
you like a piece of cake?
You know what? That would be lovely.
So... yeah. Thank you, mum.
It is. It's lovely.
Thanks.
They've seen you wearing
those clothes, right?
Yeah. Yeah.
So where's his jacket?
Right, you need to burn that.
And that gun, we need to toss it
in the river right fucking now.
Alright? Go on, fuck off.
You're... uh... you're unbelievable.
Albie? Whoever was in that pub, we have
to find out who they are, alright?
And get hold of them and just unravel
whatever they've said to the police.
Right, what we want to do is get Pat and
Bender and send them down in there.
That bartender I know her, right?
You know her?
Alright, well, bring her to me.
I'll deal with her myself.
Alright? Go on, fuck off.
Oh, where is everybody going?
Oh, mum, it's late. It's late. I
wanted them out of your hair, y'know.
You should get some bedtime.
Why don't I give you a life home? Come on.
Oh, it's alright. I am home.
I've made the bed up for him.
He's not well.
He's, uh... He's got a fever.
He's gonna stay here tonight.
Teddy, you like to stay with him?
Thanks, that would be very nice.
Thank you, Violet.
Whatever he's done...
He's your brother.
Yeah.
Well, ummm...
Here's your Stemetil, mate.
You should take that.
Do you know what? I'm going
to have to go, actually.
I left the lads at work...
and I have to clean up.
So I'm going to say g'night.
G'night.
Teddy, couldn't do us a favor?
Could you be useful?
When you takes his pantses off tonight...
and his shirt... can you burn them?
Yeah, and check in with me?
- Yeah.
- Good lad.
Night, mum.
Night.
He's lovely, isn't he?
Not even Scotland Yard could ignore
murder on the street.
Nipper was back on the case.
Gentlemen, your attention please.
Now you've been told that we are
conducting a high-level investigation...
into a major corruption allegation.
In fact, we're going down into
the sewer after the Krays.
Any man with any objection...
come and see me.
See that lamppost up there, right?
That was known as the safety
point during the war, right?
So if you could run to that lamppost...
You knew that you could
make it to the air raid
shelter before the bombs
started dropping.
One night, right, me and Ron, we
just stood there and we watched.
And we saw the old Stanton House get
blown to bits. They were still in it.
It's a wonder you lived through it.
Yeah... yeah, especially Ron, y'know.
Every time trouble came on top, he was
always dragging behind, innit he?
Well, he's got plenty of trouble now
if the stories are true.
I heard it on the street, Reggie.
My own family
and you didn't tell me.
Yeah, well, y'know, I didn't
want you to worry, did I?
I don't worry about Ron.
What are you planning to do about it?
I can't let him go to prison, am I
Why not? Why not?
Why not? Because he's my
brother, that's why not.
He'll still be your brother in prison.
No.
No, Frances, look. He belongs
here, right, he belongs with us.
He belongs to you, me and his family.
This is his home, alright?
Y'know, I've been looking
after him since we
were little boys. It's
just the way it is.
You can still look after him in prison.
And he doesn't belong
here, and you know it.
Right.
Right. Well, you just don't understand.
Yes, I do. No, you don't. You
don't understand. Yes, I do.
You once told me that you
don't owe the world a
thing. Well you don't owe
Ron a thing, either.
My loyalty for my brother is how I
measure myself, do you understand?
What about your loyalty to me?
Is that not a measure?
So... what is going on
with your eyes right now?
Are you on something?
Are you taking something, Frances?
Are you taking...
you taking pills again? Is
that what you're doing?
Let's have a look.
No, stop it.
Oh hello, look at that.
Jesus Christ, Frances, how many
of these things are you on, ey?
No wonder you're not
making any sense.
You're popping pills everywhere.
You're a pill-popper.
And who made me that?
What? A pillpopper?
So let me get this straight. What
you're saying is that in order
for us all to be free, yeah, that
we all have to be on our own?
That's great, Frances. That's...
I'll go with that.
Listen... talk to that barmaid.
Yeah?
Tell her when they line the
suspects up across from
her to point the finger at
Ron and say, "That's him."
"That's the man had to
ought to have done it."
Alright?
Where are you going?
Home.
What about me mum?
Fuck your mum!
Take your time.
No.
The man who shot Cornell is not here.
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure.
Please, can someone just take me home?
Miss.
I swear it, though. I smelt something...
I don't know what it was.
But I caught funny looks in the court.
The judge...
I think he stinked, it was.
Right? Am I right or am I wrong?
Am I wrong, Reg?
It goes to show you that you can give a dog
a bad name...
but when that dog's name is Kray, he
might bite you back. Well done, Ron.
Justice is done.
Welcome home.
To discipline.
Take one, Vi.
No.
Give her a pink wafer.
Somebody has to eat them.
What did you tell her?
Yeah, I just said that you might want
to think about your children, y'know?
I wish I could make you go away.
Well, good luck with that, Frances.
Yeah, good fucking luck with that.
Holy cameroon.
The fuck is she doing?
It surprises me that some
people are still uhh...
still survive these days.
See you later, Albie.
Are you alright?
Yeah, go on.
Are you alright? You look
like you're struggling there.
Help me.
Help you?
Well, what are we doing?
Help me put the top on.
Well, I'm not sure I can help you, y'know?
Reggie, please, it's going to get ruined.
I can't, y'know? I'm a club owner.
Y'know what I mean? I can pick a nice
model, right, and a nice color...
but I'm not very good at it. I'm
not a mechanic, am I, y'know?
I'm more of a gangster.
Isn't that right? Yeah?
Please, help me. Please, help me?
Yeah...
Please.
Please, Reggie.
Alright, let's help you.
Go on then.
How about that?
That looks a bit fucking
fucked to me, mate.
Speaking of...
You look like shit and all.
Yeah...
What are you doing?
Reggie, stop it! Stop it!
Reggie.
Alright. Stop what?
Reggie, please. Don't. Please don't.
Please... no.
Please. No!
Stop it!
Life goes on without me.
Where are you going?
I'm leaving Reggie.
Oh, that is a shame. He'll
take that very hard.
Please get out of my way, Ron.
Unless you'd prefer me to stay.
Go on, boys.
Go upstairs.
Would you like me to
help you with your bags?
No, thank you.
Oh, come on, don't be daft.
Look at the size of you. Look at
the size of me. C'mon. Come on.
You know, Frances, sometimes
to achieve greatness...
You do. You have to cut off a
little piece of yourself...
No matter how much it hurts in order
to grow. In order to move on.
It takes courage and I admire that, y'know?
To be honest, you're
getting out just in time.
You think so?
Absolutely, yeah.
There are so many people
that know so much about us.
Not you, of course.
Most people hate us.
Sooner or later someone's going to talk
and that will be it. It'll all be over.
That wouldn't be so bad, would it?
I think God ought to cut us some
slack, though, don't you think?
Yeah, I'm sure God will.
That is, uh... that is bang out of order.
That's not how we were brought up.
Not at all.
Ron, I've got to go.
Yeah, of course you do.
Listen here, Frances,
alright, we both love him, alright?
We've both made the effort.
So we should just have to see what happens
when we get there.
Where?
Heaven.
Goodbye, Ron.
Goodbye, Frances.
Listen here...
I always liked you, Frances.
I always did.
Because you have the ability
to see into the future.
You do. And that's the same as me.
Bye, now.
Hello, Reggie.
How are you?
Yeah, you alright, Frank?
Long time no see, ey?
Yeah, I'm walking straight, y'know?
Oh yeah?- Yeah.- That's nice, innit?
That's nice.
What can I do for you?
Frances here?
It's just that, y'know,
I've been outside
your parent's house the
last couple of weeks.
They haven't told me that
she left so I, y'know...
I've been standing underneath
her her window like a fool.
Yeah, she's here.
Yeah, I know.
Reggie, I...
What?
I haven't seen her like
this in a long time.
She's delicate.
Right.
Alright. Well you tell
Frances to come out
here. I want her to come out here.
Go get her.
Reggie, I'm not going to let you see her, alright.
Don't fuck about.
Frances, go back inside.
What are you doing?
Do not worry. It's OK.
Hello, Reggie.
Hello, Frances.
Have you got a moment?
So that we can chat?
It's alright.
Are you sure about this?
Go in, son. Go put a kettle on.
Frankie, come home.
I am home.
At least until I find somewhere else.
I can't go and live with my mum.
Well what can I do to change your mind?
You can't.
I've changed my mind about one
thing, though. What's that?
I do want you to remember me... always.
That I existed... that I once walked
beside you. What are you on about?
Frankie, come on.
I always imagined... I thought that
we might have a child or two, y'know?
Why?
So you could use them to threaten me?
No.
Because I still love you.
No. No, it's just a thing
you say out of loyalty for
something that didn't
exist in the first place.
Not true. Loving you is the only
thing that holds me together.
Y'know, I dreamt that we could live
beyond the place that we were meant for.
But you're a gangster
and you love being one.
No. No, Frances, listen.
Please let me make amends for the suffering
and the pain that I have cause you. Please.
Please.
Just let me take you somewhere.
Somewhere?
Yeah, anywhere. Anywhere you want.
Yeah, just the two of us.
So we can be together.
It'll be like our second honeymoon.
Or not. Just so that you can
know that I can change.
To be fair, I have... I've changed.
All I'm saying is that the center of the
world can be anywhere you want it to be.
Anywhere.
Ibiza.
Who?
Ibiza. Let's go there.
I like the way the word sounds.
Yeah. You know what? I like
the way the words sounds too.
You want to go to Ibiza?
I'll get the tickets today. I'll book them today.
God doesn't ask if we accept this life.
There is no choice.
Life is forced upon you.
The only choice is how you live it.
Or not. That's a choice as well.
A cup of tea can solve anything.
A bit under the weather? Tea. You've left
your husband? Tea is the answer.
Frances, no Frances. What
have you done? Frances!
In case you thought, "at
least Frances survived
or she wouldn't be telling
us this tale."
Well, now you know.
But I was free at last.
God finally cut me some slack.
Where is she?
In her bedroom.
That afternoon Reggie would
drink himself insensible.
What do you do after
all, when the only person
who could ever get to you is gone?
A cup of tea?
I don't think so.
One big hat.
Go on, sit down. Don't stand around there
looking like some kind of lamppost.
Squeeze in.
Sweat it. What don't we have. A bottle.
Go on. Go on, Gordon.
You wanted to see me, Ron?
Yeah, I do actually.
I want you to kill someone for me, alright?
I'm going to give you a thousand pounds.
Leslie.
There's 500 there, right, so that's half.
Yeah? You get the rest when it's done.
You count it all, cos it's all there.
And you can put it in your little pocket.
That's for you.
Go on, put it in your fucking pocket.
We know you ain't got any money.
Don't be daft.
Who is it?
Mum, wait here.
Stop, Mum. Leave it.
You killed her.
You killed my daughter, you bastard.
Spending a hundred
pounds a week on flowers
won't bring her back. Murderer.
You'll fucking rot in hell, Reggie Kray.
McVitie, what are you doing here?
I've got a message for you... from Ron.
Back.
Shall I send a solicitor
or have you seen to that?
I want my wife and children's
safety guaranteed.
Payne.
He's given them everything.
Names, dates, times.
Documents, the lot.
They'll put two and two together...
and send a dozen witnesses
into protection.
Nipper, uh...
Yeah, Nipper, what?
The barmaid. He got the barmaid back in.
She ain't coming out.
Where's Ron?
Oh, yeah.
This is a piece of of me, this.
Oh yeah. I love this song.
It's your favorite.
Oh fuck it, everybody...
What?
He still goes through, Ian. Oy.
Don't get him started.
Fuck it.
Well, thank you for asking.
Cheer up, twinkletoes.
It's nearly Christmas.
Why don't you have a little
dance or something, y'know?
What is the point of
coming out to a party like
this... if you're not
going to enjoy yourself?
I'm waiting for Jack the Hat.
Oh, right. What's he been doing?
Has he been
waving his shotgun around
in the clubs again?
What did you think going after
Leslie Payne was going to get us?
What do I think?
You heard.
Well in case you ain't realized, I don't
fucking answer to you, sweetheart.
There he is. Come on. C'mon, Ron, show
us that stuff. I've got the moves.
Hello, hello. Where the birds at?
It's Jack the Hat.
Mr. Bender, how are ya?
Nice to see you.
Esther?
Jackie.
I should never have let you go,
that was an absolute mistake.
I'm going to get myself a drink.
And then I'm going to come back
and I'll tell you why I shouldn't
have let you go. Promise.
Ron.
Teddy.
Hang on, Ron, look. Jack's here.
What's your story this morning, Dorice.
Here, Jack. A cigarette.
I quit on the way down the stairs.
You got something on your mind, Reg?
Yeah. Yeah, you're on my mind, mate.
Leslie Payne?
What the fuck were you thinking?
Ey? You've ruined this.
I don't know what you're on about.
Don't fucking lie to me.
I'm not going to fucking
let me be treated this
way. - How do you want
to be treated, Jack?
Ron?- Shut up.
He ain't going to fucking help you, is he?
You've got a tin of worms
in your head, mate.
Don't take it out on me
what happened to Frances.
What's that? What did you say?
It's not my fault
that Frances killed
herself. I never sold
her the fucking pills.
Oh, you've got to be joking.
Are you fucking joking? Reggie.
Go on.
Fucking shoot him.
Say that again, go on.
Reggie.
Say her fucking name.
I dare you.
Frances.
Why would you do that?
Because I can't kill you, no matter
how much I fucking want to.
Reggie?
Reg, look at me.
What the fuck's wrong with you?
You kill a geezer in a room full of people.
Are you fucking mad?
Ey?
Ey, what?
Reggie once said that the center of the
world could be anywhere you like.
Even here, in the East End of London.
The world is quite like London. It's not
good. It's not bad. It just is.
There's no morality or dishonor.
Just your own lonely code...
until your race is run.
Until the end.
Until we're all just ghosts of the
people we once thought we were.
Reggie spent 33 years in prison
for killing Jack McVitie.
Through all of those years, until the end,
he carried a pair of tickets with him.
Reggie, my prince. We were supposed
to go to Ibiza, after all.
Credits to cobbcobb for the Subtitle
Fixed & Synced By MoUsTaFa ZaKi